you
We're here at Radio Tech Con, Radio Tech Con is the UK's annual conference for the audio and radio technology community.
The community we have here is so important.
It's a really brilliant place to network, meet with colleagues in the UK and from beyond.
We share ideas and inspire new projects.
The sessions range from everything to do with studio builds, transmission, cyber security, and also all the bits in between.
Welcome to TechCon.
still want to have gone back to the historical record and pick the things that fit in with their narratives.
Something like carbon accounting.
Ultimately, collaboration has to be the long-term goal with everything.
Also, you're facing the wall, you might want a 180.
Oh, hello.
Yellow, yeah.
What has the transmission adjudicator ever done for me?
A lot has probably happened since your radio station very first went on a smart speaker.
Going to some of the other kit that you need to run Europe's largest radio station this is the traffic and travel answer phone and it's worked so hard.
And my work is basically trying to make speech technologies fair and inclusive.
I wanted to create an immersive experience where the audience could lie down and take some time out and be surrounded by sound.
When I was there, we had to introduce a big orange light right in front of the presenter to remind them that that fader was open.
There will be a quiz at the end.
This is the end where there will be a quiz.
Hello everyone.
Good night from TECCOM.
See you next year.
Being here is really good, there's a wide range of people all the way from up-sea level executives all the way down to people just starting and it's really good to see a big overview of the industry.
I keep coming back to Radiotechcon year after year after year because of the absolute breadth and diversity of the speakers taking to the stage.
The people speaking are not only showing me things that I've wandered about, but also things I've never even considered new.
The talks I've been lucky enough to have time to listen to after travelling down here have been excellent.
And the great thing about this conference is the extent to which people chip in with questions.
They want answers to take back to their radio stations.
I'll definitely come back again, so I'm looking forward already for the next Radio TechCon.
It really is a conference that covers pretty much everything in such a neat little package.
It's an absolute highlight of my year.